Holy Laplace is the creator of our world.
And when she departed our world,
she gifted the people with special powers.
Do you know what those are?
Skills.
Correct. Skills.
Let us give thanks to Holy Laplace
as we enjoy our bounty for today.
Thank you for the food.
Why aren't you eating? Do you feel all right?
Holy Laplace doesn't play fair.
The holy knights and warriors
have amazing skills...
So why do I have such a weak one?
I bet that's why I was abandoned.
In the old times, when Holy
Laplace protected the world,
there were no skills or stats,
nor did monsters exist.
Back then, everyone was equal.
I wish I had been born back then...
I've searched nearby, but I can't find her.
I see...
I'll check in town, too!
Sahara...
Where have you gone?
Come on, keep crying! Make some more noise!
You're gonna be a toy for the holy knights!
Dammit, this is gonna be such a pain.
You're gonna be okay now.
Hunger Boost
Come on, this is our chance
to get out of here.
I run into guys like you, sometimes.
Dumbasses who waltz in here outta
some misguided notion of justice.
Well, look at you!
You gonna be able to fight
while protecting the runt?
I need to at least get her to safety.
But where is that?
I've got an idea, Fate.
Go ahead and back away.
He thinks you're weaker than him.
We'll take advantage of that confidence.
O-Okay.
You knock those boxes down,
and you'll be the one I bury first.
You ever think about how, if I kill
your stupid ass in front of the kid,
she'll become totally obedient?
Now, Fate!
Just had to make it hard...
Now you're gonna die.
Sharp Edge, huh? That's not good.
Fate! Strike him down through his weapon!
That's the plan!
No way!
You said she was going to the holy knights.
Answer me. Who was it
that had you kidnap this girl?
I'm not saying a damn thing...
Talk! Who's the piece of trash
that hired you?!
Fine! I'll tell you!
Who was it?!
Hado! Hado Vlerick!
You're okay now.
Yeah.
Hungry now that you've relaxed?
Wanna get something to eat?
Uh, what's your name?
Sahara.
I'm Fate.
Okay, let me treat you to something.
I'll take two, please.
Sure thing.
Here.
It's hot, so be careful.
I told you to be careful...
It's good.
I've never had meat before.
You can have mine, too, Sahara.
Okay!
Sahara!
Sister!
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Fate!
Is everything all right?
Well...
I don't think anyone's ever thanked me before.
Because I've got a waste of a skill, too.
Your skill is weak, too?
I just get hungry.
Your tummy...?
That's right.
Sahara, no matter how hard things get,
if you can laugh them off,
one day you'll find happiness.
Even me?
Yeah.
Fay...
No matter how hard things get,
if you can laugh them off,
you'll be happy one day.
Someone like me?
Yeah.
Back then, I didn't understand.
But Dad telling me that...
helped me make it to this point.
Which is why...
I want Sahara to survive, too.
Looks like you've got One-Handed
Sword Technique now, too.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Strength Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Concealment, One-Handed Sword Technique,
Congrats on your first technical skill, Fate.
Is that a good thing?
Yeah.
With technical skills, you get tech-arts,
which are like secret techniques...
In this case, you're able to
attack twice in the space of one strike.
That's the Sharp Edge you mentioned?
Wait, then if he had been
able to actually land his—
You'd have been in big trouble.
Hell, you'd probably be done for.
You could've warned me!
A hero was in the middle
of saving a little girl.
What kinda jerk interrupts that?
I'm no hero!
If I had known, I wouldn't have risked it.
Sure, sure. Don't go getting embarrassed
just because you showed off.
Shut up!
The truth is, battles come down
to luck of the moment.
There's no guarantee
the stronger person always wins.
So I had luck on my side this time?
I want to get stronger...
Strong enough that I can win
without getting lucky.
I was meaning to ask, Fate.
Tomorrow's your first day working
for the Harts, right?
Yeah.
You're gonna go looking like that?
I forgot to buy clothes!
Don't drop me, dammit!
Be a little more careful!
Did you hear the news?
Sir Mason was struck down
by a Divine Dragon in Galia.
A warrior friend of mine had
the news, so it's certain.
What happens to the Hart family, then?
Lady Roxy will succeed him.
But Sir Mason was the one
keeping the holy knights
from going completely out of control...
I'm not sure that even Lady Roxy
can keep them in line.
You mean the Vlerick siblings?
Never good news with them.
I only like talking about pleasant topics.
How's Fate been?
He used to drop by after work every day.
So this is the holy knight district...
This place is huge.
Fate!
I've been waiting.
I've been waiting. I'm so glad you came.
What's the matter?
Uh, you're just... so pretty.
I was a little... speechless.
Well...
I suppose it's good
that I dress up, occasionally.
You've cleaned up quite nicely yourself, Fate.
Nah...
Come, right this way.
A grave?
Father, this is Fate, who will be
working here starting today.
I'm sure things will be lively
around the manor again now.
Is that...?
My father.
Five days ago he encountered a Divine
Dragon in Galia... and passed away.
Galia is a continent that's
dominated by monsters.
One of the holy knight's major duties
is keeping them contained.
That duty fell to the Hart family, this year.
A dangerous task, but not one
that should've been deadly.
But... a Divine Dragon, that hadn't
left its lair in over a thousand years...
My father's force was killed to the last man.
I had no idea.
In a situation like that,
she's still been looking out for me...
And I had no idea.
Don't look so sad, Fate.
I am the head of House Hart, now.
Let's work together to make it a joyful place.
Can I count on your help?
Yes. It'd be my pleasure.
Wait! If I touch her now...
It's worrying.
Telepathy will activate!
What is it?
Haru!
Haru, this is Fate.
I'm Fate Graphite. It's nice to meet you.
I'm Haru, chief maid for the Hart estate.
I ask you to comport yourself in a manner
befitting a servant of the Hart family.
Okay...
Meat!
So meaty!
Wow.
He must really like meat.
A manner befitting
a servant of the Hart family...
Hey, don't forget to take a break!
Right, Mr. Oliver. I'll get some rest
after I wrap up here.
Try not to overdo it, now.
It's already been a week
since you started here...
Yes, Mr. Minerva.
At first, I thought you were a weirdo
who was always talking to a sword...
And you were shaking when you ate meat!
It'd been five years since
I had any! Give me a break!
Come on, kid, we just had lunch.
Did you actually eat?
Of course I did!
I guess it's a growth spurt...
Mr. Fate.
Ms. Haru.
The mistress is calling for you.
Sure. Right away.
Back to work for us.
Right.
This is weird.
I actually had something to eat.
Have you gotten used to working here, Fay?
I'm feeling hungrier and hungrier...
Fay?
I won't be able to hold back much longer.
Fay!
What's the matter, Fay?
Fay.
Dad...
Oh, sorry.
My late father would call me that, too.
You lost your father, too?
Yeah. He was killed in a monster hunt...
Just like mine.
Why "Fay," though?
It's a nickname, for Fate.
Remember what I said about us making
the Hart estate a joyful place?
You're basically one of the family!
F-Family?!
M-Me and Lady Roxy...?!
I think I'd rather be Fate!
Request denied.
What... is happening...?
Fay? Fay!
My room...?
Please take tomorrow off
from work and be sure to rest.
Lady Roxy...
Hey, Greed.
Yeah?
What's happening to me?
It never got this bad before.
I could hold it together.
But now...
You're just now asking?
The die's been cast, friend.
Once the Gluttony skill gets a taste
of souls, there's no stopping it.
There's not?
Right. The more you devour,
the stronger you get,
and the more you devour, the more you want.
You're destined to seek out souls
to consume until the day you die.
And... if I don't?
You'll starve to death...
or lose control and start
attacking anyone in your path.
Anyone?!
That just... makes me sound like a monster!
Here's a little tip.
When your hunger approaches its limit,
it'll be visible in your eyes.
I'll tell you again: the die's been cast.
There's no turning back.
All right, let's hunt a lot, and earn a lot!
They smell delicious for some reason...
Probably because your
Hunger Boost has kicked in.
Is that what these red eyes are?
Yeah. Hunger Boost is a temporary power that
enables effective use of the Gluttony skill.
You'll have better night vision,
be able to track prey by scent...
And weaker prey will
be terrified, and paralyzed.
I see.
No wonder the goblins have
just been standing there...
I'm going to help myself, then!
Not enough...
Let's head on over to
the Hobgoblin Forest, then.
How much more do I need...
before I'm free of this hunger?!
Looks like that did it.
I never wanna feel like this again.
In that case, you'll need to hunt
monsters every now and then
and feed souls to Gluttony.
Yeah. I guess I will.
What the—?
What is that thing?
A Goblin king.
Goblin king?
He doesn't have much
of an edge on you, stat-wise.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Health Regeneration
What's this "Health Regeneration" skill?
It heals your wounds.
With it, you'd be able to keep fighting,
even if you get injured.
Well, I definitely want that.
What are you freaking out for?
Humans are a fine meal for monsters.
I understand that, but...
Slow and stealthy, okay?
I know.
Now, get him!
Nice, you got the drop on him.
Stop spacing out! Dodge!
You're not gonna beat him by running, man!
But that club is—
It's nothing to fear! Put your trust in me!
Got it! I will!
Now! Let him have it!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Increasing stats.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Concealment, One-Handed Sword Technique,
Two-Handed Sword Technique,
Strength Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost (Med)
Skill Health Regeneration has been added.
Health Regeneration
I'm exhausted...
Nicely done.
With your stats, I should be
able to access my first level.
Your first... level?
It's another form of mine.
If you hand over your stats
as an offering to me,
I can provide you with new functions.
A new form? I'd like to see that.
Then hand over the stats.
Okay. How much do you need?
Everything you've gained since meeting me.
All of that?!
What part of "greed" didn't you understand?
That's too greedy! Never mind.
If you don't unlock it,
you'll lose the right to wield me.
You can get stronger on your own
or make me strong, too,
so we can work together.
Time to choose.
Right now...
It's not much of a choice.
You're the only partner for me.
Well said. You won't regret this, pal.
I can feel the power leaving me...
My stats... are being stolen.
So this is Greed's new power?
A magic bow.
Magic bow...?
There's been someone eyeing
you up for a while now.
Perfect timing. Let's take a shot at him.
Where are the arrows?
Draw on the bow,
and they'll appear on their own.
You can aim wherever, and it'll still land.
Perfect for a novice like you.
Wow...!
Goblin king ears.
That should keep you fed for a while.
Roxy's Inspection
"Roxy's Inspection."